-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 潇妹纸
翻译: 海盗爱热水 捞盐 RK翔 噹噹fun饭
校对: 影子
阿富汗 赫尔曼德省
Moving 964 southeast, over.
蜂鸟正向东南964方向移动
Hummingbird drone.
完毕
Roger. They're not sure what that impacted.
收到 他们还不确定战况
Make sure it wasn't one of your friendlies, Roger.
确保他们不是友军 完毕
Red Hotel six, this is Longhorn.
红色旅馆六号 这是长角牛号
I see possible contact.
可能要交火了
That was right where they were making contact from,
报告红色旅馆指挥中心 这里就是
Red Hotel Tower.
其中一方的基地
There's an RPG coming from the east.
东面有火箭推进榴弹袭击
4-2-0, this is 4-2 Charlie.
420 这是42C
- Message over.  - Send, over.
- 完毕  - 收到 请讲
4-2 Charlie, are you aware at grid 4-1?
42C 注意到41区的情况了吗?
Only thing that was bad about it...
只有一个坏消息...
I know...
我知道...
There's been an ambush...
他们被伏击了...
Do you copy, over? Sergeant Smith, do you copy?
听到吗? 史密斯中士 能听到吗?
4-2 Charlie contact involving small arms fire on vehicle.
42C的车辆遭到轻武器攻击
There are three guys running out there at the back.
有三个人从后面逃跑
Yep, he's got a weapon on the right.
没错 他有武器
Roger that. Hummingbird can see it.
收到 蜂鸟看到了
He's got a weapon.
他有武器
He's still shooting up in the air right now.
他现在还在朝空中开枪
We see him.
我们看到他了
Sergeant Smith, I have good arcs on your position.
史密斯中士 我能很清楚地看到你的位置
- I believe he's British.  - He's shooting.
- 我猜他是英国人  - 他在开枪
蜂鸟
Echo 3-5-2, over.
E352 完毕
Installation Provost Marshal report A-R-6-3-0-1-0.
宪兵司令部报告AR63010
Sergeant Joseph Smith.
约瑟夫·史密斯中士
伦敦
Absconded from Stanbrook Military Hospital Secure Wing.
从坦布鲁克军事医院安全翼潜逃
Diagnosed with combat stress.
被诊断为战斗压力过大
Filed as Department of Defense, long-term missing person.
国防部档案记载为长期失踪人员
一年后
二月
Sorry, mate.
抱歉了 哥们
Taxman!
收税了!
All we want is your cash and your rocks.
我们只收钱和可卡因
Joey, don't fight back.
乔伊 千万别还手
Run, Isabel!
伊莎贝尔 快跑!
Hi, this is Damon.
嗨 我是戴蒙
I won't be available at this number
十月一日之前
until October the first.
我都不用这个号码
If you need me, you can call my agent Paul
有事就打给我的经纪人保罗吧
or reach me on my New York number.
或者打我纽约的电话
212-555-9898.
号码是212-555-9898
That's 212-555-9898.
重复一遍 212-555-9898
You have no new messages.
您没有新留言
您的水费单
连接指令
坦佩罗银行
内附密码
余额
请稍等
Anybody lost or needs direction?
有迷路的或需要指路的吗?
Anybody lost or needs...
有迷路的或需要...
Oh!
哦!
Get off, get off!
走开 走开!
Don't do it!
住手!
Happy birthday, Cristina.
生日快乐 克里斯蒂娜
Actually, it was two days ago, but thank you.
其实两天前才是我的生日 不过还是谢谢
Happy birthday, Cristina.
生日快乐 克里斯蒂娜
Actually, it was two days ago, but thank you.
其实两天前才是我的生日 不过还是谢谢
生日快乐 克里斯蒂娜
谢谢
No alcohol.
不许喝酒
I'm looking for someone.
我在找人
Joseph? Joseph, where did you get those clothes?
约瑟夫吗? 约瑟夫 你哪来的这些衣服?
Her name's Isabel.
她叫伊莎贝尔
They saw her.
他们看见她了
I've come to save her.
我是来救她的
Joseph, did you rob someone?
约瑟夫 你去抢劫了吗?
I had some luck.
我只是交了点好运
Maybe God, you know?
也许是上帝的旨意?
God gave me this.
上帝给了我这些
Joseph, I'm going to call David,
约瑟夫 我要打给
my police liaison officer.
我的警务联络官大卫
This is for you, sister.
这是给你的 修女
You're okay.
你是个好人
Buy something nice for yourself.
给自己买点好东西
20, 40, 60, 80, 100.
20 40 60 80 100块
20, 40, 60, 80, 200.
20 40 60 80 200块
20, 40, 60, 80, 300.
20 40 60 80 300块
20, 40, 60, 80, 400.
20 40 60 80 400块
450, 500.
450块 500块
Sister Cristina.
克里斯蒂娜修女
So, do you know how much is there?
你知道那是多少钱吗?
£500.
500英镑
A donation is a donation.
捐赠没有区别
I don't see the quandary.
我不明白你有什么为难的
He's quite famous among them.
他在那群人当中挺出名的
They say he was a commando.
他们说他是个突击队员
He killed people in Afghanistan.
他在阿富汗杀过人
That's what soldiers do.
那是军人的职责
It doesn't mean he's a thief.
这并不代表他是个小偷
Did he say where he got the money from?
他说没说是从哪弄到的钱?
He said, "Maybe God."
他说"也许是上帝的旨意"
Anyway, what do you think the police themselves
再说 如果你把钱交给了警察
would do with it if you handed it in?
你觉得他们会怎么处理?
They'd just share it out and drink it in the pub.
他们只会把钱分了 然后去酒吧喝酒
Add it to the nourishment front door at Christmas, get them all jumpers or something.
圣诞节的时候把钱捐给施膳处 给他们买些新衣服什么的
Actually, he told me to buy something for myself.
其实 他告诉我给自己买点东西
I thought perhaps maybe I could use
我想也许我能用上
just a small proportion of it.
其中的一小部分
You see, there is something I have been praying for.
我一直在祈祷能得到一些东西
You're a good and holy woman, Sister Cristina.
你是个圣洁的好女人 克里斯蒂娜修女
If the money's an answer to a prayer,
如果钱能实现你的祈祷
how can it be wrong?
那会有什么错呢?
Let me put it this way.
我这么说吧
I've not written anything down about this in the book.
我没有记录任何有关这次谈话的内容
One for Maria Zielinska.
一张玛利亚·泽林斯卡的票
One what?
一张什么?
One for the Maria Zielinska farewell performance.
一张玛利亚·泽林斯卡告别演出的票
I'm afraid it's all sold out.
很遗憾 票已经全卖光了
Sold out?
卖光了?
But it isn't until October.
可这还没到十月份呢
It sold out online in two hours.
在网上两个小时之内就卖完了
Online.
在网上
We do still have one box available.
但我们还剩一个包厢
A box?
包厢?
On Tuesday, October first.
十月一日 星期二那场
And how much is a box?
那一个包厢多少钱?
A box for the farewell performance
告别演出的包厢票
is £500.
是500英镑一张
Contact! Contact!
交火! 交火!
Contact!
交火!
Possible contact.
可能要交火了
Hummingbird drone, over.
这里是蜂鸟 完毕
Yeah, he's got a weapon on the right.
没错 他有武器
Hummingbird can see it. He's got a weapon.
蜂鸟看到了 他有武器
He's still shooting up in the air right now.
他还在朝空中开枪
We see him.
我们看到他了
Can we just cut the guy off?
我们干脆跟他中断联系吧?
Do you copy?
听到了吗?
Sister.
修女
I'm afraid you're too late for soup.
抱歉 你来得太晚 汤已经发完了
I'm not hungry.
我不饿
I need medicine.
我需要药
You're hurt?
你受伤了吗?
I need antibiotics.
我需要抗生素
I'm not allowed to dispense antibiotics.
我没权利分发抗生素
But you do it for people who can't get into the system.
但你会帮没有医保的人吧
- Go to emergency.  - I can't.
- 去急诊室  - 我去不了
Why not? If you don't want to give your name,
为什么? 你要是不想透露姓名的话
just call yourself Smith or something.
就说自己姓史密斯什么的
That would be a mistake.
那也行不通
- Why?  - My name is Smith.
- 为什么?  - 因为我就姓史密斯
Jones, then.
那就换琼斯
Sister...
修女...
I'm on the run from a court-martial.
我正在逃脱军事法庭的制裁
I was in a Special Forces unit.
我曾经服役于一个特种部队
There'll be no forgiveness.
军事法庭可不会赦免我
How do you know it's antibiotics you need?
你怎么知道自己需要抗生素?
I've got two broken ribs.
我断了两根肋骨
There's an infection around one of the breaks.
有一处感染了
If it spreads to the bone, I'll die.
如果感染扩散到骨头 我会死的
I've been wounded before.
我之前受过伤
If you drink alcohol with these, they won't work.
如果你用酒服药的话 就没有药效了
I'll need painkillers.
我需要止痛药
Give me something with dihydrocodeine.
给我点含有二氢可待因的药
Yes, sir.
明白 长官
I've asked around about your friend Isabel.
我打听了一下你的朋友伊莎贝尔
How'd you know about Isabel?
你怎么知道伊莎贝尔的?
Last night, don't you remember?
你不记得昨晚了吗?
Did I come here last night?
昨晚我来过吗?
Do something stupid?
我干了什么蠢事吗?
You said you'd had some luck.
你说你交了些好运
"God," you said.
你说是"上帝赐予的"
You don't believe?
你不相信吗?
So how do you explain those new clothes?
那你怎么解释那些新衣服?
I don't.
解释不了
So what'd you find out about Isabel?
那你打听到什么关于伊莎贝尔的事了?
She doesn't come for food anymore.
她不再来施膳处了
If you see her, give her this.
如果你看到她了 给她这个
Tell her she can come to me.
告诉她可以来找我
Tell her she can be safe.
告诉她我这里很安全
- Who lives here?  - Me.
- 谁住在那?  - 我
- Did you break in?  - I fell.
- 你破门而入的吗?  - 我掉进去的
Did you hurt someone?
你伤害别人了吗?
Only myself.
只伤了我自己
Do you know the boys say you're an angel?
他们都说你是个天使你知道吗?
Good night, Joseph.
晚安 约瑟夫
The solid sterling silver.
实打实的纯银
You've got lots of pieces of solid sterling silver and, of course...
这里有很多块纯银 当然...
there we go... you can see all of that
这里... 你可以看到这些纯银的部分
from your hat pins to your...
从你的帽针到你的...
uh... to your... shepherd's hook,
呃... 到你的... 牧羊钩
your... your clasp, your crimp beads,
你的... 你的扣子 卷珠
and six meters of elastic,
有六米的伸缩性
one large and one small gift pack.
一大一小的礼品包
Showers good.
不怕弄湿
40s, Cromarty, Forth, Tyne, Dogger.
不管是在福蒂斯 福斯 泰恩河 道格
Easterly or northeasterly
不管是东方风格还是东北风格
four or five, occasionally...
偶尔绕上四圈或五圈...
Bible tells us, you know, in Gethsemane,
圣经告诉我们 在客西马尼
talking to God and wanting to not go through with this thing
跟上帝交谈 不想经历这般苦难
and hesitating, you know.
犹豫着
And as all these incredible things,
这一切不可思议的事情
Judas going to the priests...
犹大去找神父...
伊莎贝尔 给乔伊打电话 0207 946 0362
Joey, it's Isabel.
乔伊 我是伊莎贝尔
There's no need to look for me. I'm okay.
不用找我了 我很好
And I'll just cause trouble.
我只会给你惹麻烦
I've agreed to work for them for a few weeks
我已经同意给他们打工几个星期
until I've got enough for a deposit on a nice place.
直到我存够一笔钱 能租个好地方
Then I'll go back up north.
然后我就回北部了
Thanks for looking after me, Joey, and for thinkin' of me. When I get away from London,
谢谢你想着我 还来找我 乔伊 我离开伦敦的时候
I'll call you if you're still there.
如果你还在伦敦的话 我会打给你的
I've gotta go.
就这样吧
You have two messages.
您有两条留言
I've agreed to work for them for a few weeks
我已经同意给他们打工几个星期
until I've got enough for a deposit on a nice place.
直到我存够一笔钱 能租个好地方
Then I'll go back up north.
然后我就回北部了
Thanks for looking after me, Joey,
谢谢你想着我 还来找我
and for thinking of me.
乔伊
When I get away from London,
我离开伦敦的时候
I'll call you if you're still there.
如果你还在伦敦的话 我会打给你的
I've gotta go.
就这样吧
You have no more messages.
您没有留言了
三月份
I know there is someone there 'cause I saw you go in.
我知道屋里有人 因为我看见你进去了
I'm gonna call the police.
我要叫警察了
Who are you?
你是谁?
Damon said he was gonna be in New York all summer.
戴蒙说他整个夏天都会在纽约
I'm Damon's boyfriend.
我是戴蒙的男朋友
One of 'em.
其中一个
He said I could use his flat while he was away.
他说过他不在的时候 我可以住他这儿
Are you a model?
你是个模特吗?
Sometimes.
有时候是
He didn't say anyone was gonna be staying.
他可没交代过有谁会住这儿
Do you have his number in New York?
你有他在纽约的号码吗?
No, he keeps himself very private.
没有 他很注重自己的隐私
Pity, you could've called him.
真可惜 原本你可以打电话给他的
Do you have a number?
你有他的号码吗?
He doesn't give it to me.
他没给我
In case I call him late at night.
以防我大晚上给他打电话
- I'm Tracy.  - Joey.
- 我叫翠西  - 我是乔伊
Joey Jones.
乔伊·琼斯
Damon said I should stay here for the summer,
戴蒙说我应该在这儿待上一个夏天
get my life back together.
重整旗鼓
So that's what I'm gonna do.
我听他的 就准备这么办
Whew.
呼
Fuck.
该死
Joey, there's trouble.
乔伊 有人闹事儿
Fucking dickhead's trying to throw us out.
他妈的蠢蛋居然赶咱们出来
Is he fucking following?
他他妈还跟出来了?
Dick, mate.
你个傻蛋
- Here we go.  - It's Soho, I wanna see some tits.
- 瞧瞧  - 这儿可是索霍区 我怎么没看着娘们儿
It's late, boys.
天色已晚了 孩子们
You're gonna miss your train.
你们会赶不上火车的
Who are you, our fuckin' mum?
你谁啊 你他妈是我们老娘?
He thinks he is. Fuck me if he ain't.
他还真觉得自己是 他要不是就见鬼了
- Tits, mate.  - Fucking there's your tit.
- 奶子 老兄  - 你他妈的奶子在这儿呢
- That's right, mate.  - Here's your fucking tit, man.
- 这就对了 老兄  - 你他妈的奶子在这儿 兄弟
Hey, don't fucking touch my boy!
嘿 别他妈碰我兄弟!
Fucking leave it, mate.
别他妈管我 弟兄们
He's a fucking soft, southern fucking cunt.
他他妈不过是个软蛋南方佬
- Easy, pal.  - Fucking get off him.
- 淡定 老兄  - 他妈的放开他
- You'll miss your train.  - I'll fucking have him!
- 你会赶不上火车的  - 我他妈要揍扁他!
Come on, then!
来啊 上!
Fucking get him!
他妈的给我揍他!
Now you've missed your train.
这下你真赶不上火车了
那人是谁?
没那么奇怪
纽约的斯坦利大叔现在手下就有一个
芝加哥那个大姐手下有两个
最近他们在美国是一种身份的象征
他们干黑活儿很适合
糊弄条子很管用
他看起来杀过人
听说他当过兵
这些日子越来越难找到杀过人的中国小伙子了
他们都一门心思想读大学
我的长子就他妈在那么一家垃圾广告公司...
制作那些个破烂广告
他干得如何?
那个浑小子已经不跟我讲话了
- Monkey?  - Huh?
- 猴子?  - 嗯?
你能和这个兵仔共事吗?
没问题的 舅舅 他不怎么说话 没事的
- You wanna work?  - Yeah.
- 你想干活儿?  - 没错
You know what kind of work I do.
你知道我是干什么的吧
They say you want a driver.
他们说你需要一个司机
I got a lot of businesses.
我手头有很多生意
They say you're a hard man.
他们说你是个狠角色
It's a hard city.
这座城市需要狠角色
告诉他能赚多少就行了
Hold on!
等等!
Can we play the animal game?
咱能玩儿动物游戏吗?
Go on, then.
来吧
- Um... has it got four legs?  - Yes.
- 呃... 它有四条腿吗?  - 嗯
All right, has it got fur?
好 它有毛吗?
Yes.
有的
Um, give me another clue.
呃 再给个提示
- It's gray.  - Gray?
- 它是灰色的  - 灰色的?
Yeah.
是啊
- Is it a dog?  - No.
- 它是条狗吗?  - 不是
Um, could it eat me?
呃 它会吃我吗?
Probably.
有可能
Right, so, how many legs has it got?
好吧 那 它有多少条腿?
- Two.  - You said four.
- 两条  - 你刚才还说四条的
Are you tricking me?
你在耍我?
I hear he wants to see me.
我听说他要见我
What the fuck?
他妈的怎么回事?
New rules.
新规矩
No room service cards anywhere between
在莱塞街和皇冠区之间
Lisle Street and The Crown.
一律不准张贴客房服务的卡片
What the fuck are you talking about?
你他妈在说什么?
You're not even a fucking Chink to be giving out rules.
你他妈连个中国佬都不是 还敢给我们这儿立规矩
Show him.
给他点颜色看看
New rules.
新规矩
No.
不
Can I help you?
需要我帮忙吗?
I've got a delivery for the Angel of the Lord's Mission.
这儿有给布道团天使的外卖
45 Margheritas, 45 garlic breads,
45杯玛格丽塔酒 45块蒜香面包
45 Coke Zeroes,
45罐零热可乐
45 chicken dippers, and 45 coleslaws.
45块鸡块 还有45份凉拌菜丝
There must be a mistake.
肯定搞错了
It's paid for by Joey Jones.
是乔伊·琼斯付的钱
Okay, it's not a mistake.
好吧 那就没搞错
Who wants pizza?
有谁要比萨?
Tell your boss in fifteen minutes
告诉你老板在15分钟内
to have Mr. Choy's envelope ready.
准备好给周先生的份子钱
Also, I wanna order takeaway for delivery.
还有 我要叫外卖
It's very nice, but I've no idea what it is.
这个棒极了 可我完全不知道它是什么
I think it's probably duck.
我觉得应该是鸭子
And there's fish and chicken and pancakes.
还有鱼 鸡肉和薄饼
- And this is from Crazy Joe the angel, yeah?  - Next?
- 这都是疯子天使乔送来的 是不?  - 下一位?
Just drive, man. Just fucking drive.
管你开车 老兄 快他妈开车
That's his little sister. She won't talk.
那是他妹妹 她什么也不会说的
七月
Dawn?
道恩?
It's me.
是我
Joe.
乔
Nice suit.
穿得真不错
Me and your daughter live on £25 a week.
我跟你女儿一周靠25镑过活
Since I lost my job, I've been paying the landlord with blowjobs.
自打我丢了工作 我一直给房东口交来付房租
What have you been doing while they cut everything, Joey?
他们夺走一切的时候你都在干什么呢 乔伊?
I've been fighting.
我在奋斗
There's more where this came from.
我还会给你更多钱的
Lots more.
更多
You got my invitation.
你收到了我的邀请
Wasn't sure you'd come.
不确定你会不会来
Buying food for the boys, it's okay,
给大家买吃的还可以接受
but not this.
但这个不行
Giving me things puts me in a very difficult position.
给我东西会让我左右为难
You're not vegetarian, are ya?
你不是素食主义者吧?
Why are you lighting fires on the pavement?
你怎么在人行道上生火?
My Chinese boss sends his people here
我的中国老板派他的人到这儿来
to buy meat for his restaurants.
给他的餐厅买肉
I get three hours hanging out on the street
我有三个钟头可以在街上乱晃
doing nothing.
无所事事
So tonight I decided to have a barbecue.
所以今晚我决定来个烧烤
You used to feed me.
你过去一直给我吃的
Tonight, I feed you.
今晚 换我请你吃饭
This is a very strange thing to be doing.
这件事做起来很奇怪
I miss the smell of woodsmoke.
我想念这木柴烟的味儿
I'm guessing that you have psychological problems.
我猜你心理有问题
They put me up a mountain
他们把我扔到山上
and told me to kill people.
叫我去杀人
What'd they think would come back down the mountain?
那从山上放下来的还能是个什么样的人?
Joseph, I came here because I might have some news...
约瑟夫 我来这儿是因为我可能有...
about Isabel.
伊莎贝尔的消息了
They found a girl.
他们找到一个女孩儿
Last night, my police liaison officer
昨晚 我的警方联络员
gave me this photograph.
给了我这张照片
She was found in the river.
她是在河里被发现的
They need help with identification.
他们需要人帮忙辨认身份
She was from the north, that's all I know.
她是北方来的 我就知道这些
Did you love her?
你爱她吗?
We shared a box.
我们挤一个垃圾箱
We'd just keep each other warm.
为对方取暖
Will you talk to the police?
你会跟警察谈谈吗?
Fuck the police.
去他妈的警察
Joseph, I'm really sorry to bring such awful news.
约瑟夫 带来这样悲痛的消息 我真的很抱歉
Where in the river?
在哪段河里发现的?
The city, near to Canary Wharf.
市区 卡娜利码头附近
One of those rich guys.
某个阔佬干的
Yes, they think she was killed by a client.
是的 他们认为她是被嫖客杀死的
- The police give a shit?  - Of course they do.
- 警察们还在乎这些?  - 当然
David is a good man.
大卫可是个好人
Really? He's a "good man."
是吗? 他是个"好人"
Good, good. Good for him.
好啊 对他来说是不错
Good.
好
In the fucking river!
在他妈的一条河里!
If you dare to be angry about Isabel...
要是你胆敢为伊莎贝尔动怒...
you're a hypocrite.
那你就是个伪君子
I've asked around about your job
我打听过你的工作
for the Chinese boss.
你在中国老板手下干
They say, "Crazy Joey deals drugs."
他们都说"疯子乔伊做毒品买卖"
I just deliver the stuff. I don't touch the stuff.
我只负责运输 我自己从不碰那玩意儿
The autopsy said Isabel "touched the stuff".
验尸官说伊莎贝尔"碰那玩意儿"
Maybe stuff you delivered.
还可能是你给运送的
You don't put those things together in your head.
你就是不会把那些事儿连起来想
You know why she ended up in the river?
你知道她为什么死在河里?
Because that's what the river's for.
因为河就是干这个用的
To wash away girls when they're finished with them.
完事儿以后用来冲走那些女孩儿
I see what's happening in this fucking city.
我算是看出这鬼城市他妈的怎么了
How many people you feed these days, huh?
你这些天给了多少人吃的?
You give them soup.
你给他们汤喝
They want their lives back!
他们要的是自己原本的生活!
Joey, when you were out of your head on drugs
乔伊 几个月前你毒品磕高了
a few months ago, you gave me some money.
神志不清的时候 你给了我些钱
I've spent it on something for myself.
我把它用在了自己身上
I haven't been able to sleep properly since.
自那以后我就没睡过一个安稳觉
I... I called my sister in Warsaw.
我... 给在华沙的姐姐打了电话
She sold some of the possessions I left behind.
她变卖了些我留在那儿的私人物品
I don't need this.
我用不着这个
I'm really sorry about Isabel.
伊莎贝尔的事 我真的很抱歉
I know you cared for her,
我知道你在乎她
but think about all the other Isabels.
但想想其他和她处境相似的姑娘
Start to do the right thing.
洗心革面吧
It is honest money. I cleaned it for you.
这是勤劳挣得的钱 我为你洗净了
Use it to start an honest life.
用它来重新开始生活吧
I want you to have this.
收下吧
I'm gonna do a lot of good things this summer.
我这个夏天会做很多好事
Give people what they want.
给人们他们想要的
I thought you might want a dress.
我觉得你想要一条裙子
Joey, I'm a nun.
乔伊 我是个修女
I used to wear a uniform.
我过去也穿制服
Don't mean a thing, you just take it off.
意味不了什么 你脱掉就是了
If it looks beautiful on you,
你穿上肯定很漂亮
then God would say it's okay, wouldn't He?
那上帝也不会反对 是吧?
I will put it in the bag of clothes for Africa.
我会把它跟捐给非洲的那包衣物放在一起
My guest this week is Baroness Glennis Baker,
这周 我的嘉宾是格兰尼斯·贝克女男爵
a emeritus professor of psychology.
一位心理学荣誉退休教授
She has specialized in the health and welfare
她特别关注听力障碍人群的
of people with learning disabilities,
健康和福利
advising on policies and influencing...
提议制定政策 并影响了...
Fuck.
该死
Yeah!
嘿!
Your cash and your rocks, boys.
快把钱和可卡因交出来 小子们
Don't remember me, do you?
不记得我了 是吧?
Not surprised.
挺正常的
I've changed.
因为我变了
You've got a knife...
你们有把刀...
I've got a spoon.
我用这把勺子
Who killed Isabel?
谁杀了伊莎贝尔?
Go on, Joey. Show 'em. Show 'em!
上啊 乔伊 揍他们 给他们点颜色瞧瞧!
Who killed Isabel?
谁杀了伊莎贝尔?
I don't know.
我不知道
You're only alive because I need information.
我可是为了消息才不杀你的
An eye for an eye.
以眼还眼 以牙还牙
You tell me what happened to her,
你告诉我她怎么死的
or I'll kill you with this spoon.
不然我就用这把勺子干掉你
Some guy used to rent her regular.
有个人包了她
Beat her up.
打她
He used to ask for her.
他之前一直点名要她
He went too far.
他玩过火了
Name.
叫什么
We don't use names.
我们不用名字的
Describe him to me.
给我描述一下
- Ah!  - Describe him to me.
- 啊!  - 给我描述一下
He was about 30, city boy,
他大概30岁的样子 城里人
scar over his eye.
眼睛上方有块疤
That's all I know.
我就知道这么多
You get any trouble from these two again,
要是这俩再不老实
you tell Crazy Joe, okay?
你就告诉疯狂乔 懂了吗?
埃文·布斯 您被邀请参加八月22日晚6点到8点30的私人展出 提供鸡尾酒和香槟
我有关于杀了伊莎贝尔凶手的消息 需要告诉警方 到时候见 乔伊·琼斯
Jesus.
天啊
Fuck.
该死
You look...
你看上去...
Your note said you had information
你信上说 你有关于杀了伊莎贝尔凶手的消息
for the police about Isabel's killer.
需要传达给警方
That is the only reason I am here.
我只是为了这个来的
And I put on this dress because
而我穿这条裙子
it is the only dress I have.
是因为我只有这一条裙子
And don't think I won't send it to Africa,
不要以为我不舍得捐给非洲
because I will.
因为我之后就会捐掉
They think my name's Damon, by the way.
顺便说一句 在这里我叫戴蒙
Please don't remind me.
别提醒我了
- I think I might faint.  - What?
- 我感觉我会晕倒  - 什么?
I haven't eaten anything all day...
我一天都没吃东西...
worrying whether or not I would come.
一直在想到底要不要来
Also, I didn't realize
再说 我也没想到
there would be so many naked men.
这边有这么多裸男
Look, I arranged to meet you here
其实 我把见面地点安排在这里
because I thought you might like the photographs.
是因为我觉得 你会喜欢摄影相片的
I didn't realize there'd be photographs
我也不知道这里展出的是
of men's... penises.
男性... 生殖器摄影
Sorry.
对不起
Joey, actually, I do like photographs.
乔伊 其实我很喜欢摄影
I take photographs... usually of nature.
我也拍照片... 但都是自然题材
Penises are nature, I suppose.
那我觉得 阴茎也是自然的一部分啊
Yes, I suppose they are.
好吧 就算它是一部分吧
So what'd you tell the Mother?
那你对圣母有什么要说的吗?
I lied, I lied, I lied.
是我说谎 我说谎 说谎
So what information do you have?
那你到底有什么信息?
Tell your policeman to look for a guy around 30.
告诉警方去调查一个30岁左右的男性
He has a scar above his eye.
眼睛上方有道疤痕
Works in the city.
在城里工作
Should I write this down?
我要写下来吗?
That's all I have.
我就只有这些消息
Okay...
好的...
30 years old, scar above his eye,
30岁左右 眼睛上方有疤痕
works in the city. Got it.
在城里工作 记住了
We haven't been introduced.
我们没介绍过吧
I'm Karl. What's your name?
我是卡尔 请问你是?
Just looking around.
我就四处转转
I'm told the invitation you handed in at the desk
有人跟我说 你给前台的请帖
was addressed to Damon Coldfield.
是寄给戴蒙·科菲尔德的
I happen to be Damon's photographic agent.
我就任于戴蒙的摄影部门
He's in New York.
他现在人在纽约
Who the hell are you?
你到底是谁啊?
我发现 我终于想明白了
I think you're a bit drunk.
我觉得你是有点醉了
Yes.
的确有点
I'm having a crazy patch.
我有个很大的遗憾
Starting when I bought the ticket.
都是从我买了那张票开始
What ticket?
什么票?
I used your money to buy a ticket to a ballet.
我用了你的钱 买了一张芭蕾舞演出的票
That's a pretty wicked thing to do.
这样做的确不怎么虔诚
But, you see...
但是...
I've loved her since I was a little girl.
我从小时候就喜欢上她了
Loved who?
喜欢谁?
Maria Zielinska.
玛利亚·泽林斯卡
She's 42 and still dancing.
她42岁了 可还在跳舞
She is who I always wanted to be.
她才是我的梦想
She is who I should have been.
她才是我的目标
但看看她把我领到了哪里
I'm in a silk dress in an alleyway...
我现在站在羊肠小道 穿着丝绸长裙...
with a gangster.
身边陪着个强盗
- Whoa!  - Oop!
- 哇哦!  - 哦!
And I'm drunk.
我还喝醉了
Are you still a gangster, Joey, or did I change you?
你还是个强盗吗 乔伊 还是我让你有所改变了?
Just having a crazy patch, too.
我也有个很大的遗憾
There are things that I have to do.
有些事我必须去做
When the summer's over, I'll stop.
等今夏过去之后 我就停手
Because of me, yes?
是因为我吗?
I have to think I'm doing good.
我要说服自己 我在做好事
Your excuse for wearing a pretty dress.
这是你为了穿漂亮裙子的借口吧
When does Damon return?
真的戴蒙什么时候回来?
October the first.
十月一日
Then it's fate.
真是命运弄人
What is?
怎么回事?
When I say it's fate...
我说是命运的时候...
I should really say it's God, but I don't.
我应该说是上帝的安排 但我没这么说
You know why?
你知道为什么吗?
Because I'm not so sure that God is there anymore.
因为我不确定 上帝还和不和我们同在
That's the truth.
这是实话
我依上帝的名义 逃避照顾自己
I think I'm going to throw up.
我觉得我快吐了
Oh.
哦
No, I'm fine.
不 我没事
Sister, I'm Catholic.
修女 我信天主教的
I'm not your sister.
我才不是什么修女
I'm drunk and I'm up against the wall.
我醉了 我靠着墙
30...
30岁左右...
a scar above the eye...
眼睛上方有疤痕...
works in the city.
在城里工作
A massive 50% off.
五折促销
Rain jackets half price.
雨衣半价
Fleece half price, T-shirts half price.
羊绒衫半价 T恤半价
Walking shoes half price.
鞋子也半价
A massive 50% off.
全场五折
Joey...
乔伊...
H... how are things?
你... 你最近怎么样?
Things are okay.
蛮不错的
Have you heard from Damon?
你有戴蒙的消息吗?
Yeah, he's okay.
有啊 他很好
You seem so together now.
你看上去好多了
I'm really together now.
的确 我重新振作了
You're like a different person.
你都快大变样了
So, Joey...
乔伊...
are you exclusively gay?
你是只喜欢男人的吗?
You know, it's interesting...
这问题还真有点意思...
recently...
最近...
I've found myself attracted to...
我发现我有点喜欢上...
nuns.
修女了
Who the fuck are you?
你他妈的是谁啊?
You owe Mr. Choy money.
你欠周先生的钱
What the fuck do you know about Mr. Choy?
你知道个屁周先生啊?
He's my boss.
他是我的老板
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
Mr. Choy only employ Chinese.
周先生只收中国人
Tell Mr. Choy I'll send him a check.
告诉周先生 我等会儿寄支票给他
I'm taking the cash.
这钱我拿走了
我不喜欢他这样子
我们这里四个人呢 没事的
Give me the fucking cash.
把钱给我
Step out of the way, my friend,
走开点 伙计
and let me take some of what you owe in cash
我就拿一小部分钱
as a gesture of goodwill.
表示一下你的诚意
No!
不准!
Please don't hurt him!
请不要伤害他!
That money belongs to my family.
这是我养家的钱
Vincenzo, no!
文森泽 住手!
Of Mamarita Restaurant...
麻麻丽塔餐厅发生...
18 Clancey Street. That's 1-8 Clancey Street.
地点柯兰瑟街18号 重复一遍 柯兰瑟街18号
known by the name of Joey Jones...
嫌犯为乔伊·琼斯...
no known address. Approach with caution.
无居住地址 请小心接近
Reported connection to the Angel of the Lord
据称他跟修道院的
Homeless Mission, Covent Garden.
流浪汉收容中心有联系
Is there a problem? You are scaring my clients.
有什么问题吗? 你吓到我的客人了
We're looking for someone.
我们在找一个人
Calls himself Joey Jones.
自称乔伊·琼斯
We've been told he used to come down here.
我们被告知 他经常来这里
They said you'd know where to find him.
据说你知道在哪里能找到他
Let me help ya.
还是我来吧
What are you doing here?
你在这里干嘛?
I just lied to the police.
我刚刚还对警察说谎了
You haven't changed at all.
你一点都没变
If I could do something else, I would do it.
我有什么可以补偿的吗 我会做的
What did the policeman say?
那警察说了什么?
Do you gave him the description?
你告诉他们凶手的样子了吗?
He laughed at me.
他听后就嘲笑我
He said it was "too vague."
他说这也太模糊了
He said, "Tell Joey Jones to come
他还说"告诉乔伊·琼斯
and speak to us himself."
让他自己来说个清楚"
You mean they can't be bothered to fucking look
你是说 就因为她是个妓女
'cause she was a whore.
所以他们就不管了
The truth is...
其实...
the police are more interested
警察对你是谁
in finding out more about you.
更感兴趣
You're becoming famous, Joey.
你成名了 乔伊
And Isabel isn't famous?
那伊莎贝尔就不出名了吗?
You really are a hypocrite.
你可真虚伪啊
You beat Taxman so bad he's still in hospital.
你对那人下手这么狠 他现在都还在医院
You're not just an angel,
你不是个天使
you're God Almighty dispensing justice.
你是全能上帝正义的化身
Yeah, well, I believe in justice.
好吧 我的确相信正义
Sometimes you have to make it happen yourself.
有时候 正义是要自己争取的
I'm not the only hypocrite here.
又不是只有我是伪君子
Want a kiss?
想亲一个吗?
- Sorry.  - Get out of my car.
- 对不起  - 下车
It's a van.
这是货车
I suppose you think it was very funny that I got drunk.
我感觉 你以为我喝醉了是件很开心的事情
I've been drunk myself on occasion.
我时不时会灌醉自己
What exactly happened?
发生什么了?
You don't remember?
你不记得了?
It's all a blur.
迷迷糊糊的
You asked me to kiss you, so I kissed you.
你让我亲你 我就亲你了
You didn't have to kiss me
我让你亲
just because I asked.
你也不一定要亲的
I wanted to.
我想亲
Why did you want to?
为什么你想亲?
That's a really stupid question.
真是个蠢问题
Look in the mirror.
你看看镜子就知道
It's not my fault that I'm fucked up.
我搞砸了 那也不是我的错啊
For a nun, your language is pretty bad.
作为个修女 你可真是口无遮拦
So whose fault is it?
那是谁的错呢?
He was my gymnastics instructor.
那人是我的体操教练
It was in Warsaw.
还在华沙的时候
It was my father who made me do gymnastics.
我爸爸让我去练体操
I wanted to be a ballerina,
但我想为芭蕾舞演员
but he said no.
但他不同意
If I had become a ballerina,
如果我连芭蕾舞的话
it wouldn't have happened.
一切就不会发生了
My instructor began to...
我的教练开始...
He began to do it when I was 10 years old.
我10岁的时候 他就开始骚扰我了
He did it 17 times.
前后17次
It was going to be the 18th time.
差点就18次了
For a very long time, I believed I belonged in hell.
很长时间 我相信自己属于地狱
Because I was so young...
因为我还小...
they decided not to send me to prison.
他们决定不把我送进监狱
Instead, they sent me to a convent.
而是把我送进了修道院
Joey, I...
乔伊 我...
I have never told this to anyone before.
我从来没和其他人说过这些
Want me to drive?
我来开车吧?
I want someone to drive.
我的确需要人来帮我开车
Here will be fine.
这里就行了
How will you get home?
你怎么回家呢?
I'm a gangster. I'll steal a car.
我是个强盗 我偷辆车就行
I'll walk.
我走回去啦
It's a lovely morning.
今早天气不错的
Cristina, in the end,
克里斯蒂娜 说到底
I just took off my uniform and ran.
我只是脱了军装 逃走了而已
And look what happened to you.
看看你身上都发生了什么
Sister Cristina, I am deeply shocked.
克里斯蒂娜修女 这太让我震惊了
You filled in the Africa application.
你填了去非洲支援的申请表
My preference is for the Valley Mission in Sierra Leone.
我希望能去塞拉利昂的峡谷地区
But what about your work here
那你这边的工作怎么办?
at the Soho Mission?
施膳处的工作呢?
Africa was always part of my life plan.
非洲支援一直是我人生计划的一部分
Yes, in two years.
没错 那是两年之后的事情
I want permission to move it forward.
我希望可以把此事提前
But why?
但为什么?
I am finding there are too many distractions here in London.
这儿有很多事儿让我分心
You're blushing.
你脸红了
It's very warm in here.
这里有点热
It's even warmer in Sierra Leone.
塞拉利昂更热
Hot, even.
非常热
I will wear a hat.
我会戴帽子
You have applied to leave in this quarter.
你申请这个季度就离开
I am ready to leave any time after October the first.
10月1以后我随时可以离开
Joey, they said you wanted to speak to the boss.
乔伊 听说你想见大老板
Come with me.
跟我来
Sit.
坐
Madame, you know everything that happens
女士 你知道
in your back garden.
你们后院儿起火了
If a man pays for girls and he's violent,
如果有个嫖客很暴力
he soon becomes famous.
他现在很出名呢
We refuse to deal with them.
我们拒绝和他们继续合作
The Russians will just charge double.
俄罗斯人会收双倍价钱
I understand you have a blacklist of violent men.
我知道您有份黑名单
I'm looking for a very violent man
我正在找
who attacks girls.
他们中的一个人
He's young. Around 30.
他年纪不大 30岁上下
And he has a scar above his eye.
眼睛上方有道疤
He wears very expensive suits.
他穿得很绅士
We know him.
我们知道他
The description is not too vague for you?
看来这个人对于你们来说并不陌生?
We have a business to protect.
我们也是在做生意
Madame, would you be able to
女士 您能查到
find out the name of this man?
这个人的名字吗?
他能为我们做什么?
可以给他别人不接的活儿
Hmm.
恩
A favor for a favor.
公平交易
伸出左手
握拳
- Did they tell you?  - Tell me what?
- 他们告诉你了吗?  - 告诉我什么?
They didn't tell you.
看来没告诉你
No, no, stop!
不 不 住手!
- Ah!  - They didn't tell you.
- 啊!  - 他们没告诉你
Stop.
住手
58.
58个
Some of them are kids.
有些还是孩子
And some of them are girls. You want one?
有的还是女孩儿 要一个吗?
I also asked for information.
我要的消息呢
It's coming, okay?
马上给你 行吧?
醒醒 欢迎来到伦敦
你们的梦想都会实现
十月一日
It's the latest. Do you know how to work it?
这是最新款 会用吗?
Yes, of course.
当然
You could afford to get a professional to do this.
你应该请专业摄影师给你拍
Yeah, but I wanted you.
没错 但我想让你给我拍
So who are the photographs for?
拍的照片给谁?
My daughter.
我女儿
You have a daughter?
你有女儿?
Nine years old.
9岁了
I came here with her once when she was small.
她小的时候 我带她来过这里
She might remember.
她可能还记得
I want her to have some photographs of me
我想让她留着
looking like a normal man.
我看上去比较正常的照片
What do you think?
怎么样?
Like this?
这样?
Smile.
笑
Why?
为什么?
Okay, actually, you look okay.
好吧 看上去还行
Do I look like a good man?
我看上去像个好人吗?
What do you mean?
什么意思?
I want her to think I'm a good man.
我想让她认为我是个好人
Yes, you look like a good man.
是 你看上去是个好人
So take a picture.
拍照吧
Did your daughter ask for photos?
你女儿找你要的照片?
No, but when she's older,
不是 但是等她长大了
I want her to have something to remind her of me.
这些照片能让她想起我
You won't see her?
你不会再见她吗?
I don't think I'll look like this for much longer.
我觉得我可能体面不了多久了
Why not?
为什么?
Why shouldn't you stay like this?
为什么不能一直这样?
Just take a picture.
拍照吧
You should have one like this.
别动 再来一张
More natural.
很自然
The businessman drinking his morning coffee.
生意人正在喝早安咖啡
Such a successful man.
多么成功的人
So rich.
非常富有
- Charitable.  - Of course.
- 十分慷慨  - 当然
She will be very proud of you.
她一定会以你为豪
Enough.
好了
I said enough.
我说好了
At last a laugh.
笑着来一张
There. I am changing you.
看吧 我改变了你
Send those ones to me.
给我寄些照片
I'll take them with me to Africa.
我会带去非洲
You're going to Africa?
你要去非洲吗?
A valley in Sierra Leone where there is no water.
塞拉利昂的一个山谷 那儿没有水
When do you leave?
你什么时候走?
Tomorrow.
明天
So this is the end of my crazy patch, Joey.
乔伊 这是我最后的疯狂
And I've decided I want to end it with you.
我想与你共度这段时光
Sport coats, shorts...
运动外套 短裤...
half price. T-shirts half price.
半价 T恤半价
I've got rain jackets half price.
雨衣半价
Fleece half price.
羊毛衫半价
Walking boots half price. Trousers, half price.
短靴半价 裤子半价
Keep the change.
不用找了
half price. A massive 50...
半价 特大优惠
half price. Rain jackets half price.
特价 雨衣半价
Hello? Who's there?
你好? 谁在里面?
Hello?
有人吗?
Cristina!
克里斯蒂娜!
Who the bloody hell are you?
该死的 这是谁?
I don't know who you are, but open this door.
我不认识你们 但快给我开门
Did you hear me? I said open the door.
听到了吗? 我说给我开门
Cristina.
克里斯蒂娜
There's enough money in here to get us away.
这儿有足够的钱让咱们离开
We could go anywhere in the world.
咱们可以远走高飞
No, Joey...
不 乔伊...
if you want to be a good man,
如果你想成为一个好人
be a good man.
那就努力去成为一个好人
Joey, will you come with me to the ballet tonight?
Joey 今晚你能和我一起看芭蕾舞剧吗?
I have a box. There is room for two.
我买的包厢票 双人座
Tonight at 7:00.
今晚7点
My time here at this mission
在救助中心的工作
has been a fulfilling time.
让我收获颇丰
Surprises all along the way.
伴随着惊喜
Our mission has had some failures.
有不尽如人意的地方
Some tragedies...
有悲剧产生...
the poor girl Isabel.
如可怜的伊莎贝尔
But we have also had successes.
但也有成功的方面
And we have also had some who,
尽管不知道他是如何出现的
in spite of how it may appear,
但是终有一个人
give us reason to hope.
给我们带来了希望
Who are you?
你是谁?
I've got something for your mother.
我给你妈妈带了些东西
And something for you.
也有送你的
Can I just hold your hand for a minute?
我能跟你握个手吗?
Ruby, who is it?
露比 谁来了?
You be good, okay?
要听话 懂吗?
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士们先生们
and the farewell performance of Maria Zielinska.
今晚玛利亚·泽林斯卡的告别演出
Tonight's performance will begin in five minutes.
5分钟后开始
Please take your seats.
请进场就座
Closing doors.
关门
Absolutely, no.
根本没有的事儿
Ladies and gentlemen, Maria Zielinska.
女士们先生们 有请玛利亚·泽林斯卡
Max?
马克思?
Max Forrester?
你是马克思·弗莱斯特?
Yes. Who are you?
是的 你是哪位?
How was your bonus this year? Was it good?
今年的分红怎么样? 还好吗?
It was very good.
非常好
Are you from Cisco or American Eagle?
你是来自美国思科的还是北美鹰的?
No. I'm from down there.
都不是 我从那下面来的
Listen, can I talk to you for a minute?
我能和你聊两句吗?
I was actually just getting some drinks.
我想去拿杯饮料
- Who are you?  - Who am I?
- 你是谁?  - 我是谁?
Let me think...
我想想...
Oof!
唔!
What the... what the hell do you want?
你... 你究竟想干什么?
I think you should know how it feels to be down there.
我想让你知道下面是什么感觉
What?
什么?
A reported fatality. Paramedics are on the scene.
一则死亡新闻报道 救护人员正在现场救援
Witnesses report he was pushed or thrown from the roof.
目击者称受害者被从楼顶推下去
Military Police reference blotter AR630.
宪兵资料第AR630号记载
Surveillance footage matches visual of Joseph Smith.
经监控录像对比 疑犯名为约瑟夫·史密斯
Department of Defense, long-term missing person.
隶属国防部 长期失踪人员
- Do you have a visual?  - Negative, no further sightings.
- 能看到他吗?  - 不能 看不到了
What are you doing here?
你在这儿干嘛?
I'm waiting for Maria Zielinska.
我在等玛利亚·泽林斯卡
There was a party after the show.
演出之后有个晚会
I want to see her walk to her car.
我想看着她上车
Let me explain.
我给你解释一下
When I'm sober...
我清醒的时候...
when I'm healthy and well...
身体强壮...
I hurt people.
杀了很多人
I'm lethal.
我是杀人机器
I drink to weaken the machine they made.
只有通过喝酒才能减轻负罪感
I've finished the work I had to do.
我已经完成了我要做的
And already, look.
已经完成了
You see 'em?
你看到了吗?
Hummingbirds.
蜂鸟
Hummingbirds were there that day.
那天蜂鸟就在那儿
Do you copy?
能收到吗?
Surveillance drones saw what happened.
无人侦察机拍到了发生的一切
Roger that. Hummingbird can see it.
收到 蜂鸟看到了
He's got a weapon...
他有武器...
He's shooting up in the air right now.
他还在朝空中开枪
你抓错人了
不是他干的!
Please, please!
求求你了!
The enemy killed five of ours...
敌人杀死了我们五个人...
so I killed five of theirs.
所以我也杀了他们五个人
The first five I could find.
看见人我就杀
I left the father hanging.
他们的父亲是被我吊死的
You see her?
你看见她了吗?
She is my witness.
她就是我的证人
Sister.
修女
"Dear Cristina,
"亲爱的克里斯蒂娜
I just wanted to say thank you for taking the photographs.
很感谢你为我照的照片
Considering it's me in the pictures,
我不上相
they turned out pretty well.
但你已经拍得很好了
I gave all the best ones to my daughter,
我把最好的几张给我女儿了
so you're left with the ugly ones
所以你就留着这些
and the scary ones. Sorry.
不好看的吧 抱歉
I've sent Damon the money I took from his account
我已经把戴蒙账户里的钱还给他了
and added some extra for rent.
也给了他利息
I left the boys at the mission some cash for pizzas.
我给施膳处的孩子们留了些钱买披萨
And I sent details of the people smugglers
也已经把走私贩的资料
to the police.
给了警察
I also rid the city of a bad man.
我也改过自新 不做坏人了
I know that doesn't make me a good man,
我知道这并不能让我成为一个好人
but I tried to do the right thing.
但我努力了
Now I'll go back to the street and disappear.
现在我要重回属于我的地方 然后默默消失
I was alive again for one summer.
这个夏天 我重获新生
I'm glad I spent it with you.
很感谢你陪在我身边的日子
I hope Africa treats you well.
祝你在非洲一切都好
All my love, Joseph Smith."
爱你的 约瑟夫·史密斯"
Surveillance camera profile matched to Joseph Smith.
监控录像发现约瑟夫·史密斯
Target heading eastbound on Brewer Street
目标沿着布鲁尔大街向东
towards Glasshouse Street.
走向暖房街
Absent without leave.
消失不见了
File zero-four-zero for profile and visual.
文档040 视频资料
I repeat that's east... east on Brewer Street.
重复 布鲁尔大街东边方向
matches visual of Joseph Smith.
发现约瑟夫·史密斯
Approach with extreme caution.
小心靠近
I think we have him.
我们找到他了
Okay, target in sight. Go.
目标进入视线范围 上
Yeah, we got him. Take him.
抓住他了 抓住了
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 潇妹纸
翻译: 海盗爱热水 捞盐 RK翔 噹噹fun饭
校对: 影子